Guide to the University Archives Poster Collection, 1935-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - An Evening with Blondell Cummings, Duke University Institute of the Arts, undated (Box 9)
  - Greensboro Tragedy, Mary Lou Williams Center, undated (Box 9)
  - 50th Anniversary Tribute to Blind Boy Fuller, Lecture / Demonstration on Bull City Blues, Mary Lou Williams Center, undated (Box 9)
  - Mixer for Asian, Black, Hispanic and Indian Students, Mary Lou Williams Center, Flyer, 1988 (Box 9)
  - North Carolina Center for Creative Photography, Institute of the Arts, Postcard, undated (Box 9)
  - Alvin Stevenson, "Starting a Jazz Collection," Mary Lou Williams Center, Flyer, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Walter Bishop, Duke Jazz Series, 24 October 1997 (Box 9)
  - Jackie McLean, Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, 1 November 1996 (Box 9)
  - National Scholastic Press Association, All-American Honor Rating, The Chanticleer, Certificate, 1 November 1935 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Brochure, Undergraduate Admissions Office, undated (Box 9)
  - Men's Basketball Poster, Artist - Ernie Barnes, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Terry Sanford Death and Burial, News Clippings, April 1998 (Box 9)
  - Duke Poster, Undergraduate Admissions Office, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
  - Duke Brochure, Undergraduate Admissions Office, undated (Box 9)
  - Harper's Weekly, Teddy Roosevelt on the Value of Athletics, April 1894 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Basketball, Marvin Square Garden, Press Guide, 20 March 1971 (Box 9)
  - Duke Men's Basketball Awards Poster, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Duke Football Poster, 1995 Season (Box 9)
  - Peter, Paul, and Mary, Duke University Student Union, 17 October 1965 (Box 9)
  - Wendell Willkie, Address by, 14 January 1943 (Box 9)
  - Emmett Kelly Jr. Circus, 12 April 1973, presented by Duke University Union Joe College Committee (Box 9)
  - Duke Dining Services Restaurant Menu, 2007. (Box 9)
  - box 10 (Box 10)
  - You can't control the elements, Duke Women's Basketball poster, signed by Bales, Harding and Waner, 2007 (Box 10)
  - Sexual Perversity in Chicago, Flyers and Programs, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Twelfth Night, Posters, Programs and Postcards, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Blood Relations, Programs and Posters, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Riders to the Sea, Programs and Flyers, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Kudzu: A Southern Musical, Brochures, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Orpheus Descending, Programs and Posters, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Posing Naked, Programs and Flyers, 1998 (Box 10)
  - New Works for the Stage, One-Act Plays, Programs and Posters, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Have You Seen Alice, Programs and Flyers, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Lorca's Birthday, Postcards, Programs and Posters, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Robert Crumb Comix, Duke University Museum of Art, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Program for Murder, Duke Stage Company, undated (Box 10)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace; Bad Guys and Bed Fellows; Macbeth, Duke Stage Company, undated (Box 10)
  - The Miser, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Three Cuckolds, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Moonlight and Valentino, Duke Drama Broadway Preview Series, undated (Box 10)
  - Medal of Honor Rag, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Arms and the Man, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Carmina Burana, Duke University Institute of the Arts Winterfest of Contemporary Arts, undated (Box 10)
  - Baryshnikov in Metamorphosis, Duke Drama, 1989 (Box 10)
  - 1492, Duke University Broadway Preview Series, undated (Box 10)
  - Artist Descending a Staircase, Duke Broadway Preview Series, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Mud, Wax Theater Project, undated (Box 10)
  - The Double Pierrot, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Cloud 9, Wax Theater Project, directed by Ariel Julia Nazryan, undated (Box 10)
  - Cloud 9, Wax Theater Project, directed by Ben Spector, undated (Box 10)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, Duke University Program in Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Measure for Measure, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Hamlet, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Stage Door, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The House of Blue Leaves, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Love of the Nightingale, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - He Who Gets Slapped, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Miser, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Twelfth Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, Marlena Shaw vocalist, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Fifth Annual World Premiers Festival, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Second Annual World Premiers Festival, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Feminists, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Father, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Cymbeline, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Shakespeare Festival, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Thirteenth Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, Sonny Rollins, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Eighth Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, Roy Hargrove Quintet, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Eleventh Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, Stanley Jordan, 1993 (Box 10)
  - A Balagan, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - New Works for the Stage, Duke Drama, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Kaspar, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - A Marvelous Party: The Scenes and Songs of Noel Coward, Duke Drama, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Old Coots Read Genesis 1-8, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Soon Without the Moon, Duke Drama, Workshop Flyer, undated (Box 10)
  - No Exit, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Fen, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - A Folk Festival, Duke University, 1995 (Box 10)
  - New Works for the Stage, Duke Players, 1999 (Box 10)
  - The New Trial, Duke Players, undated (Box 10)
  - Arcadia, Duke Players, undated (Box 10)
  - The Illusion, Duke Players, undated (Box 10)
  - The Three Sisters, Wax Theater Project, undated (Box 10)
  - An Evening of One-Act Plays, Wax Theater Project, undated (Box 10)
  - Duke Drama Broadway Gala Series Brochure, 1989 (Box 10)
  - The Maids, Duke Drama Workshop, undated (Box 10)
  - Mad Dog Blues, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Trojan Women, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Servant of Two Masters, Duke Drama, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Third Annual World Premiers Festival, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Model Apartment, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Reckless, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Collected Works of Billy the Kid, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Merry Wives of Windsor, Texas, Duke Drama Broadway Preview Series, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Full Moon, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Thomas Hampson, Duke University Artists Series, 1995 (Box 10)
  - The Tallis Scholars, Duke University Artists Series, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Theater '94 – New Works for the Stage, Duke Drama, 1994 (Box 10)
  - King Ubu, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Second Shepherd's Play, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - The Butterfly's Evil Spell, Duke Drama, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Theater '95 – New Works for the Stage, Duke Drama, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Next Temptation, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Theater '93 – New Works for the Stage, Duke Drama, 1993 (Box 10)
  - Miami City Ballet, Duke University Artists Series, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Tokyo String Quartet, Chamber Arts Society, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Avner the Eccentric, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Van Gogh / Gauguin, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Three Sisters, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Our Town, Duke Drama, undated (Box 10)
  - Chapel, Reproduced from an Original Painting by Alan Cheek, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Lorca's Birthday: A Selection of Poems, Songs, and Farces by Federico Garcia Lorca, Duke Players, April 23-26, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 10)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar, Hoof 'N' Horn, April 16-26 (Box 10)
  - Shakespeare's Twelfth Night or What You Will, Duke Players, Oct. 24-Nov. 2 (Box 10)
  - The Tempest, Duke Players, Feb 28-Mar.8 (2 copies) (Box 10)
  - Arcadia, Duke Players, Oct. 23-Nov. 1 (Box 10)
  - Orpheus Descending, Feb. 27-Mar. 8 (3 copies) (Box 10)
  - box 11 (Box 11)
  - "Duke Fans for Dukasis," poster autographed by Dukasis (Box 11)
  - "Heart," Duke University Union Broadway at Duke, 19 January 1984, Page Auditorium (Box 11)
  - Special One Day Presentation of Original Prints, Lakeside Studio, 4 October 1972 (Box 11)
  - Free Gospel Music Concert, Duke University Museum of Art, 10 September 1989 (Box 11)
  - Two Free Gospel Music Concerts, Duke University Museum of Art, 16-17 July 1988 (Box 11)
  - Pygmies: An Epic of the Golden Age, Presented by Save the Efé Pygmies, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Our Future in Space, Symposium, Duke Program in Science, Technology and Human Values, 19-20 March 1987 (Box 11)
  - Festival for the Eno, 3-4 July 1983 (Box 11)
  - Seventh Annual Martin Luther King, Jr. Celebration, 12 January 1996 (Box 11)
  - Bon Voyage, Starring Duke Employees, DUMC, 16-17 October 1992 (Box 11)
  - Eugene Fodor, Duke University Artists Series, 14 April 1978 (Box 11)
  - No, No, Nanette, Hoof 'N' Horn, undated (Box 11)
  - Duke University Views on Two Campuses, undated (Box 11)
  - Duke Children's Classic, 29-30 May 1977 (Box 11)
  - Mike Cross, Rock 'n' Rye, 10 February 1984 (Box 11)
  - Widespread Panic, September 19, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Three Sisters, Duke Players, undated (Box 11)
  - Duke Athletics Poster, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Duke University Poster, Toomey Cartoon, undated (Box 11)
  - Raleigh's Dream, British American Festival at Duke University, 3-4 June 1984 (Box 11)
  - North Carolina Dance Theater, A Midsummer Night's Dream, Duke University Artists Series, 20-21 September 1984 (Box 11)
  - British American Heritage Quilt, British American Festival at Duke, 2 June 1984 (Box 11)
  - Third Annual Mary Lou Williams Jazz Festival, 12-14 April 1985 (Box 11)
  - Art of the Andes Pre-Columbian Sculptured and Painted Ceramics, Duke University Museum of Art, 1984 (Box 11)
  - The Budweiser Comedy Shop Tour, 15 February 1985 (Box 11)
  - Daniel Schorr on "The Right to Know," Duke University Union Major Sepakers Committee and Duke Law Forum, undated (Box 11)
  - An Adventure in Chinese Songs and Dance, 12 October 1982 (Box 11)
  - Nicolai Gedda, Duke University Artists Series, 4 November 1979 (Box 11)
  - American Dance Festival, 1979 (Box 11)
  - American Dance Festival, 16 June – 28 July 1979 (Box 11)
  - Milwaukee Ballet Company, Triangle Dance Guild, 11 October 1977 (Box 11)
  - Duke Artists Series, Spring 1976 Posters (Box 11)
  - Chaplin, A Series of Feature Classics, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Frank Zappa and the Mothers of Invention Plus Dr. Hook and his Medicine Show, DUU Major Attractions Committee, undated (Box 11)
  - Stars of the American Ballet, Duke University Artists Series, undated (Box 11)
  - The Feld Ballet, Duke University Artists Series, 12-13 November 1981 (Box 11)
  - Tommy Dorsey and His Orchestra, Arthur Boran, Glee Club and Concert Orchestra, Feature Picture – Alice Brady as "Lady Tubbs," Quadrangle Pictures Eighth Birthday Party, undated (Box 11)
  - Duke Players, Contents of Scrapbook, 1953-1960 (Box 11)
  - Kashmir and Rajasthan, Photographs by Raghubir Singh, Duke University Museum of Art, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Duke University Poster, 1920s (Box 11)
  - "The Spirit Lives On…", Duke Basketball 1978-1979 (Box 11)
  - USSR – USA Track and Field Meet and Summer Arts Festival, 5-6 July 1974 (Box 11)
  - USSR – USA: Summer Arts Festival, 5-6 July 1974, Mounted Poster (Box 11)
  - The Silent Vigil and Strike, Duke Divinity School, 12 April 1968 (Box 11)
  - Counter-Celebration, MSA, undated (Box 11)
  - What "Post"-Colonial Age??!, undated (Box 11)
  - MSA Counter-Celebration, undated (Box 11)
  - Basketball, "Return of Roy [Williams]" spoof on Lord of the Rings, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Duke Basketball (Men's), 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Duke Basketball (Men's), 1991-1992 (Box 11)
  - Duke Basketball (Men's), 1993-1994 (Box 11)
  - Duke Basketball (Men's), 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Duke Basketball (Men's), 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - The Right Stuff, 1984-1985 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Formula for Success, 1985-1986 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - 1986, A Banner Year (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Taking Care of Business, 1986-1987 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Tradition, 1987-1988 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Encore, 1988-1989 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Duke's Young Guns, 1990-1991 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Red, White and True Blue, 1989-1990 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - History in the Making, 1994-1995 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Networking, 1995-1996 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Back in Black, 1996-1997 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - NCAA Champions, 1990-1991 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Duke Blue Devils, 1992 NCAA Champions (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Blue Planet, 1997-1998 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Championship Vision, 1998-1999 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Forever, 1999-2000 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - The Big Dance, 2000-2001 (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - Duke 2001 National Champions (Duke Basketball, Men's) (Box 11)
  - The Excitement Continues, 1999-2000 (Duke Basketball, Women's) (Box 11)
  - Duke Basketball United, A2001-84 (Duke Basketball, Women's) (Box 11)
  - Net-Rageous, 2000-2001 (Duke Basketball, Women's) (Box 11)
  - 2004-2005 (autographed by team) (Duke Basketball, Women's) (Box 11)
  - Banner Year, 2005-2006 (autographed by team) (Duke Basketball, Women's) (Box 11)
  - The Road Less Travelled 206-2007 (autographed by team) (Duke Basketball, Women's) (Box 11)
  - Duke Soccer, Men's, 186 (Box 11)
  - Duke Football, 1989 (Box 11)
  - On the Rise, 2001 (Duke Football) (Box 11)
  - Airborne, 1999 (Duke Football) (Box 11)
  - Look What's Going on in Your Own Backyard, 1991 (Duke Football) (Box 11)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Team Posters, Miscellaneous, 1977-2002 (Box 11)
  - Duke University Campus Chest, Nov. 13-15 [1963?] (Box 11)
  - Mark Mallus Posters of Concerts from Events at Duke, circa 1968-1972 (Box 12)
    - Traffic and Fairpost Convention (Box 12)
    - Joe College Weekend: Mark/Almond, Seatrain, The Byrds, Hot Tuna, Taj Mahal, John Hammond (Box 12)
    - The Isaac Hayes Movement (Box 12)
    - Bread and Livingston Taylor (Box 12)
    - Leon Russell and Mandrill (Box 12)
    - Ten Years After and Yes (Box 12)